Speier, Hans; Papers ger084
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- The RAND Corporation materials, 1948-1988; 5; 130 file folders
  - Essays, position papers, memoranda, 1948-1988; 5.2; 114 file folders
    - Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or prepared under the direction of Hans Speier, Undated; 5.2.7
      - "Soviet Intentions and Disengagement (On George F. Kennan's Russia, The Atom and the West)", 1958 March 26; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 7)
      - "Disengagement", 1958 May 18; typescript, bound mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 8)
      - "Summary of Political and Economic Area Studies", 1958 December 24; mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 9)
      - "The German Crisis: A Field Report, January-February, 1959", 1959 March 20; mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 10)
      - "The Berlin Crisis", 1959 May 12; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 11)
      - "Some Observations on Political Gaming" (written with Herbert Goldhamer), 1959 October; reprints (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 12)
      - "Chronology of Events Relating to Germany and the East-West Conflict: Late 1958 to February 1960", undated; mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 13)
      - "Talk with Franz Josef Strauss, German Minister of Defense", 1960 June 14; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 14)
      - "The Impact of Military Power on the Cold War", 1960 October 31; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 15)
      - "The Future of Alliance Systems", 1961 April 4; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 16)
      - "Political Games and Scenarios", 1961 May 6; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 17)
      - "An Historical Look at the RAND Research Program", 1961 July 5; bound typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 18)
      - "The Influence of the Cuban Crisis on the Berlin Issue", 1962 November 14; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 19)
      - "Separate Peace Treaty", 1962 November 19; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 20)
      - "Short texts, 1963 (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 21)
      - "Comments on Nathan Leites' RM-3667-ISA (Draft) 'Guesses about DeGaulle'", 1963 May 16; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 22)
      - "Comments on 'Depressurization'", 1963 October 29; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 23)
      - Short texts, 1964 (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 24)
      - "Reunification, German Popular Attitudes", ca. January 1964; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 25)
      - "German Reaction to USD-SU Agreement to Cut Back Uranium Production", 1964 April; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 26)
      - "German Political Impressions", ca. May 1964; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 27)
      - "Relaxation of Tension -- German versus American Interests (Re Erhard Visit to Washington, June 1964)", typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 28)
      - "Excerpts of Document on the MLF (London, June 3rd)", 1964; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 29)
      - "Erhard-Schroeder and the Gaullist Fronde, July 1964", typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 30)
      - "Aspects of German Foreign Policy. (Notes for talk given at Institute of Strategic Analysis, London, July 13, 1964)", typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 31)
      - "Germany and the American Interest", 1964 October 13; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 32)
      - "Divided Germany in World Affairs", 1964 November; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 33)
      - Short texts, 1965 (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 34)
      - "Gelbgefahr: Immigration", ca. 1965; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 35)
      - "The Three Strands of U.S. Policy toward Germany", 1965; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 36)
      - "U.S. Policy toward the Reunification of Germany", 1965 January 26; typescripts (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 37)
      - "The Hallstein Doctrine", 1965 June 17; typescript, mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 38)
        Reprint, October 1966.
      - "Crisis and Catharsis in the Middle East", 1965 July 30; mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 39)
      - "Crisis and Catharsis in the Middle East", 1967 June; bound typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 40)
      - Short texts, 1966 (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 41)
      - "Germany, the Continuing Challenge", 1966 April; bound typescript, notes (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 42)
      - Short texts, 1967 (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 43)
      - "Germany in American Foreign Policy", 1967; mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 44)
      - "The New German Foreign Policy", 1967 April; typescripts, mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 45)
      - Short texts, 1968 (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 46)
      - Short texts, 1969 (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 47)
      - "Comments on West Germany", 1969; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 48)
      - Short texts, undated (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 49)
      - "Concealment: Pechel", undated; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.7-Essays, memoranda, position papers authored by or ), Folder 50)
    - Texts prepared for RAND by others, Undated; 5.2.8
      - "A Guide for Professional Reading by Air Force Officers", 1950 September 8; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 51)
      - Bell, Aaron. Short texts, 1953-1954 (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 52)
      - Brown, J. F. "Relations Between the Soviet Union and Its Eastern European Allies: A Survey", 1975 November; mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 53)
      - Clegg, Helen. "Reunification of Force as an Element of West German Ostpolitik, 1966-1969", 1970 January 22; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 54)
      - Crain, Ben W. "The Debate Over Innere Führung in the Bundeswehr", 1969 February 13; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 55)
      - DeWeerd, H. A. "Nassau: British Defense Policy and the NATO Deterrent", 1963 April 15; mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 56)
      - Fainsod, Merle. "Censorship in the USSR -- A Documented Record", 1956 March-1956 April; reprint (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 57)
      - HAD. "Cold War Chronology", ca. 1950; mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 58)
      - Harris, William R. "Will West Germany Get Nuclear Arms Without Really Trying?", 1971 January 14; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 59)
      - Jenkins, Brian Michael. "High Technology Terrorism and Surrogate War: The Impact of New Technology on Low-Level Violence", 1975 January; mimeograph (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 60)
      - Kecskemeti, Paul. "Leahy Slips", 1950 June 23; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 61)
      - Mendershausen, Horst. "Some Data on the U.S. Economic Stake in Germany", 1965 April 20; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 62)
      - Mendershausen, Horst. "Agreed: FRG Nuclear Abstinence No Ground for Ragged Monitoring System", 1971 February 2; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 63)
      - Wohlstetter, A. "RAND's Continuing Program of Broad Policy Study: Problems and Incentives", 1960 February 22; typescript (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 64)
      - Zagoria, Donald S. "Khrushchev's Attack on Albania and Sino-Soviet Relations", 1961 November; bound typescript (Box 10 (5.2.8-Texts prepared for RAND by others), Folder 65)
- Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by other authors, 1941-1982; 6; 85 file folders
  - Articles with no authors listed, 6.1
    - "German Radio News Bulletins. Problems and Methods of Analysis (Research Project on Totalitarian Communication, Dec. 1941)", Undated; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 1)
    - "Research Project on Totalitarian Communication, Paper No. 5: Data on a German Situation", 1942 June; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 2)
    - "A Study of War Communiques. Methods and Results". Confidential study, 1942 January (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 3)
    - "The Berlin Crisis: A Report on the Moscow Discussions, 1948", Undated; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 4)
    - "Einige Schwierigkeiten beim Schreiben in totalitären Herrschaftssystemen", 1964 February 24 (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 5)
      Typescript, RIAS.
    - "Kurt Roesch Memorial, December 5, 1984", Undated; typescript (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 6)
    - Various papers on the topic of the Governability of Democracies, 1975; typescripts, photocopies (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 7)
    - "Résumé of the Conference of the Institute For Strategic Studies on The Spread of Nuclear Weapons", 1965 February 26-1965 February 28; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 8)
  - Authored articles, 6.2
    - Abel, Theodore. "International Terrorism", Undated; typescript (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 9)
    - Bachmann, Siegfried. "Leben und Werk des Soziologen Prof. Dr. Theodor Geiger (1891-1952)", 1979 November 20; typescript (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 10)
    - Berelson, Bernard. "Communications and Public Opinion", 1948; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 11)
    - Binder, Carroll. "International Aspects of Freedom of Information", 1952 January; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 12)
    - Bowie, Robert F. "Tensions Within the Alliance. Atlantic Policy", 1963 October; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 13)
    - Brauchitsch, Walther v., Erich v. Manstein, Franz Halder, Walter Warlimont, Siegfried Westphal. "The Army from 1920-1933", 1945 November 19 (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 14)
      Typescript, Nuremberg.
    - Brodie, Bernard. "The Morale Factor in Strap Planning", 1949 August 5; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 15)
    - Bundy, McGeorge. "The Next Steps Toward Peace. Some Notes on the Two-Legged Process", 1963 September 30; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 16)
    - Dow, Roger. "Veterans' Attitudes Toward Rearmament", 1951 August 22; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 17)
    - Emmet, Christopher. "Memorandum on Policy Toward Eastern Europe", 1971 June 30; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 18)
    - Flechtheim, Ossip K. "Futurology -- The Science of Probability", Winter 1949; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 19)
    - Forschungsinstitut der Deutschen Gesellschaft für Auswärtige Politik. "Anerkennung der DDR. Die politische und rechtliche Problematik", Undated; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 20)
    - Friedberg, Maurice. "Russian Writers and Soviet Readers", 1955 May; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 21)
    - George, Alexander L. "Prediction of Political Action By Means of Propaganda Analysis", Spring 1956; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 22)
    - Gliksman, Lucja Pinczewska. "A Study of the Informative Value of Soviet Fiction (A Progress Report), 1955 November; typescripts (carbons) (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 23)
    - Goldhammer, Herbert. "Fashion and Social Science", 1954 April; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 24)
    - Griffith, William E. "The Great Globe Transformed", 1971; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 25)
    - Grudin, Robert. "Renaissance Laughter: The Jests in Castiglione's Il Cortegiano", 1973; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 26)
    - Häfele, W. "Die friedliche Nutzung der Kernenergie und der Atomwaffensperrvertrag", 1967; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 27)
    - Handzik, H. "Die Genesis der Nonproliferations-Politik der USA gegenüder den späteren Nuklearmächten", Undated (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 28)
      Teil I: 1943-1954. Bound typescript, May 26, 1967. Teil II: 1955-1963. Bound typescript, Jan. 20, 1968.
    - Hirshleifer, Jack. "Some Thoughts on the Social Structure After a Bombing Disaster", Undated; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 29)
    - Hitch, Charles. "Sub-Optimization in Operations Problems", 1953 May; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 30)
    - Hula, Erich. "The Question of Russian Objectives", 1958; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 31)
    - Isakson, Evelyn Moore. "Bernt Balchen Report Summary", 1972 July; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 32)
    - Jackall, Robert. "Crossing the Line. White Collar Crime in America", Undated; typescript (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 33)
    - Janis, Irving L. "Psychological Effects of Electric Convulsive Treatments", 1950 May-1950 June; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 34)
    - Kehr, Eckart. "Zur Genesis der preussischen Bürokratie und des Rechtsstaats", Undated; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 35)
    - Kennan, George F. "Two Speeches: 1. How New Are Our Problems? 2. The National Interest of the United States", 1951 March 1; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 36)
    - Kirchheimer, Otto, Undated (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 37)
      "Notes on the Political Scene in Western Germany". Reprint, April 1954; "The Waning of Opposition in Parliamentary Regimes". Reprint, Summer 1957.
    - Kirwin, Gerald. "Nazi Propaganda and Allied Bombing", Undated; typescript (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 38)
    - Kratochvil, Antonin. "Revisionism and its Liquidation in Czechoslovak Literature 1957-1960", mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 39)
    - Kris, Ernst/Nathan Leites. "Trends in Twentieth Century Propaganda", 1947; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 40)
    - Lasswell, Harold D., 1938-1958; reprints (11) (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 41)
    - Leites, Nathan."Psycho-Cultural Hypotheses about Political Acts."Reprint, 1948 October (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 42)
    - Lerner, Daniel. "Psychological Warfare. Sykewar against Germany, D-Day to VE-Day", Undated; typescript (carbon) (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 43)
    - Lowenthal, Leo, Fall 1956 (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 44)
      "The Sociology of Literature". Reprint, 1948; "Historical Perspectives of Popular Culture". Reprint, January 1950; (with Marjorie Fiske). "Reaction to Mass Media Growth In 18th-Century England". Reprint.
    - Luckmann, Benita. "New School Varianten der Rueckkehr aus Exil und Emigration", Undated; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 45)
    - MacMaster, Robert E. "The Question of Heinrich Rückert's Influence on Danilevskij."Reprint, 1955 February (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 46)
    - Mahling, Friedrich. "Das religiöse und antireligiöse Moment in der ersten deutschen Arbeiterbewegung (von ca. 1840-1860)", 1921; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 47)
    - Mendel, Arthur P. "N. K. Mikhailovskij and His Criticism of Russian Marxism", 1955 October; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 48)
    - Mosely, Philip E. "Soviet Research in the Social Field", 1950; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 49)
    - Mulcahy, Francis D. "Gypsy Society"; "An Analysis of Gypsy Folk Tales", Undated; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 50)
    - Nelson, Benjamin. "Science and Civilizations, 'East' and 'West'. Joseph Needham and Max Weber", 1974; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 51)
    - Neumann, Sigmund. "Conservatism: New and Old", 1957; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 52)
    - Oertzen, K. von. "Das Abrüstungsproblem", Undated; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 53)
    - Ono, Tsutomu. "Analysis of 'Kimi No Na Wa' (What Is Your Name?). A Serial Radio Drama", 1955 January 28; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 54)
    - Padover, Saul K. "Japanese Race Propaganda", Summer 1943; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 55)
    - Paechter, Heinz. "Recent Trends in the German Command Economy", 1944 September; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 56)
    - Pinson, Koppel S. "On the Future of Germany. A Survey of Opinions and Proposals", Autumn 1944; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 57)
    - Pütz, Karl Heinz. "Die amerikanische Kultur- und Informationspolitik für und in Deutschland zwischen 1942 und 1949: Eine Projektbeschreibung", 1982; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 58)
    - Schaeffler, Richard. "Krise -- Grenzfall oder Grundsituation?", 1974 December 11; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 59)
    - Schmölders, Günter. "Die politische Korruption in den Vereinigten Staaten und ihre Bekämpfung in der Nachkriegszeit", 1932; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 60)
    - Schutz, Alfred. "Symbol, Reality and Society", Undated; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 61)
    - Seaborg, Glenn T. "Our Nuclear Future: Threat or Promise?", 1965 February 5; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 62)
    - Sereno, Renzo. Notes pertaining to the subject Fools and Folly, 1965; typescripts (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 63)
    - Sereno, Renzo, Undated (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 64)
      "Obeah. Magic and Social Structure in the Lesser Antilles". Reprint, Feb. 1948; "Boricua. A Study of Language, Transculturation, and Politics". Reprint, May 1949; "Note on Gaetano Mosca". Reprint, June 1952.
    - Shils, Edward A., Undated (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 65)
      "Limitations on the Freedom of Research and Teaching in the Social Sciences". Reprint, 1938; (with Herbert Goldhamer). "Types of Power and Status". Reprint, Sept. 1939.
    - Simon, Herbert A. "Comments on the Theory of Organization", 1952 December; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 66)
    - Skulsky, Samuel. "A Theory of Time", Undated; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 67)
    - Snyder, Richard C. / Glenn D. Paige. "The United States Decision to Resist Aggression in Korea: The Application of an Analytical Scheme", 1959; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 68)
    - Sokel, Walter H. "The Changing Role of Eros in Wedekind's Drama", 1966 March; reprint (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 69)
    - Staudinger, Hans. "Erinnerungen über meine Begegnungen mit Max Weber", 1978 March 17; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 70)
    - Stikker, Dirk U. "The Fourteen and France", Undated; typescript (carbon) (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 71)
    - Strecker, Gabriele. "Meine Eindrücke in Amerika", 1946 December 1; typescript (carbon) (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 72)
    - Strube, Claudius. "Krisen und Krisentheorie", 1976 August 18; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 73)
    - Tesoro, George A. "The Bankruptcy of Fascist Economy Through the Eyes of Italian Economists", 1943 February; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 74)
    - Thayer, Charles W. "Development of German Veterans' Organizations", 1951 September 25; mimeograph (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 75)
    - von Senger und Etterlin. "Die Konferenz von Königswinter 1956", Undated; typescript (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 76)
    - Waldhorn, Herbert F. "Report on Panel: The Silent Patient", Fall 1958; photocopy (Box 11 (6-Miscellaneous typescripts and publications by othe), Folder 77)